ATHM Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6524/003 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Arranged Alphabetically
  - O, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Item 19: Our Standard, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 2)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. N.p., ca. 1800s. Image of African-Americans picking cotton in center; image of woman at spinning machine in upper left-hand corner. White lettering against red banner. 26.5 x 21 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 20: Our Standard, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 2)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. N.p., ca. 1800s. Image of African-Americans picking cotton in center; image of woman at spinning machine in upper left-hand corner. White lettering against red banner. 26.5 x 21 cm.
    - Item 21: Oxford Colored Flannels, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Yds. Middlesex Bleachery & Dye Works. N.p., n.d. Red lettering against yellow background. 25.5 x 20.25 cm.
    - Item 22: Oxford Fine Silesias, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against deep purple background. 9 x 12.5 cm.
  - P, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: P.C.T. 616, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Style _____ _____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against green background. 6.25 x 8.75 cm.
    - Item 2: Pachoug Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering against light blue background. 20 x 16 cm.
    - Item 3: Pacific Mills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Des. ____ ____ Yds. Lawrence, Mass.: Pacific Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraving? Image of woman and man (god and goddess?) in center with two jaguars. 11.75 x 15 cm.
    - Item 4: Pacific Mills, Lawrence, Mass., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Des. ________ Yds. Lawrence, Mass.: Pacific Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraving? Image of mill complex in center. Corners of label are torn. 12 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 5: Pacific Mills and Print Works Lawrence, Mass., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Des. No. ____ ____ Yds. Lawrence, Mass.: Pacific Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraving? Image of mill complex along Merrimack River. 16.25 x 11.75 cm.
    - Item 6: Pacific Mills and Print Works, Lawrence, Mass., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Des. No. ____ ____ Yds. Lawrence, Mass.: Pacific Mills, ca. 1800s. Copy 2. Engraving? Image of mill complex along Merrimack River. 16.5 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 7: Pacific Mills and Print Works, Lawrence, Mass., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Des. No. ____ ____ Yds. Lawrence, Mass.: Pacific Mills, ca. 1800s. Copy 3. Engraving? Hand-colored. Image of mill complex along Merrimack River. 16.5 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 8: Pacific Mills and Print Works, Lawrence, Mass., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      ca. 1800s. Copy D. Engraving? Image of mill complex along Merrimack River. 14.5 x 9.5 cm. This copy has been trimmed.
    - Item 9: Dog, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Palmam Qui Meruit Ferat. Trade Mark
    - Item 10: Palmer Co. Blue Drills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering and image of mill complex in center against yellow background. 24.75 x 21 cm.
    - Item 11: Palmer Company Brown Denims, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Yards. P[a]cher-Russell SC. N.p., n.d. Black lettering and image of mill building in center against yellow background. 20 x 16.5 cm.
    - Item 12: Palmer Mills shirting, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      _____ Yds. Three Rivers, Mass.: Otis Company, ca. 1850-1900. Image of mill complex in center, surrounded by white, black and light blue design. 16 x 21 cm.
    - Item 13: Palmer Mills Shirting, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      _____ Yds. Three Rivers, Mass.: Otis Company, ca. 1850-1900. Image of mill complex in center, surrounded by white, black and light blue design. 16 x 21 cm. Copy 3.
    - Item 14: Palmetto Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Lith. of Ch. H. Crosby 3 Water St. Boston. N.p., ca. 1857-1863. Silver lettering and design against white background. 12.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 15: Paragon Vest Paddings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against white background. 12 x 15 cm.
    - Item 16: Parana Fine Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering within black border against white background. 12.5 x 15.25 cm.
    - Item 17: Pards, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. Yds. WGB. N.p., ca. 1900s. Image of two leopards. Not an American label. 12 x 14.75 cm.
    - Item 18: Paris, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. ____ Metres ____ Yards ____ Gouleurs ____. N.p., n.d. Green lettering with green and gold design against white background; label very worn. In French. 6.5 x 10.25 cm.
    - Item 19: Paris, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. ____ Metres ____ Yards ____ Gouleurs ____. N.p., n.d. Green lettering with green and gold design against white background; label somewhat worn, torn in lower right-hand corner. In French. 6.5 x 10.25 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 20: Paris Qualite Imperiale, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. ____ Mts. ____. Apprel Parisien. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against white background. In French. 8.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 21: Park Mills, goods warranted, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Porter & Dickey, Philadelphia. No. Yds. Philadelphia, Pa.: Porter & Dickey, ca. 1880. Image of three women in classical dress in center with sailing ship and warehouse in background; two putti in lower corners. 11.5 x 15 cm.
    - Item 22: Park Mills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Porter & Dickey, Philadelphia. No. Yds. Philadelphia, Pa.: Porter & Dickey, ca. 1880. Image of three women in classical dress in center with sailing ship and warehouse in background; two putti in lower corners. 11.5 x 15.5 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 23: Park Mills Superior Silesia, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering with putti holding oval with lettering on his shoulder. 7 x 9.25 cm.
    - Item 24: Patapsco Heavy Osnaburg Stripes, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against blue background. 20 x 18.5 cm.
    - Item 25: Pawtucket J Vest Paddings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against blue background. 21.25 x 13 cm.
    - Item 26: Pawtucket Falls, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Pawtucket, R.I., ca. 1800s. Image of Pawtucket Falls surrounded by mill buildings against green background. 7.5 x 5 cm.
    - Item 27: Peabody Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering on banner against cream background. 8.25 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 28: Peabody Mills., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Newburyport, Mass.: Peabody Mills, ca. 1870-1900. Peabody Mills spelled out in driftwood hanging from a tree branch; two children have climbed the tree, other children, including one with a drum, march along the sidewalk. 22 x 17.25 cm.
    - Item 29: Peabody Mills Newburyport, Mass. suitings., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Geo. W. Averell Lith. 20 & 22 Gold St. N.Y. Newburyport, Mass.: Peabody Mills, ca. 1868-1899. White lettering against red banner; gold and black lettering against blue background; portrait of George Peabody (1795-1869) in upper left-hand corner. 12.5 x
    - Item 30: Peabody shirtings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Case Yds. Dennison & Co. [printer]. Newburyport, Mass.: Peabody Mills, ca. 1868-1899. Black lettering; image of dog's head with Fidelity written underneath it in center. 5.75 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 31: The Rhode Island shawl warranted all wool, 1882; Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Peacedale [Peace Dale] Manufacturing Co. Peacedale [Peace Dale], R.I.]: Peacedale Manufacturing Co. Handwritten notes on reverse dated Dec. 4th /82. Black lettering against white background; illustration in center in silver of anchor with Hope at top.
    - Item 32: Peace Dale Mills Founded 1801, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Style ____ Pat. ____ Case ____ Pc No. ____ Yards ____. J.P. Stevens & Co., Inc. Selling Agents, New York. No claims will be allowed on this piece. If imperfect may be returned within 30 days from time it is received. [North Andover, Mass.]: M.T. Steve
    - Item 33: Sample of label printed by Peerless Company, Rochester, N.Y., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      From Farr Alpaca Company. N.d. Sample supplied by printing company as example of cloth label. Gold lettering against black background. 9.25 x 6.5 cm.
    - Item 34: Peerless Shrunk, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering (faded) on very thin paper. 22.75 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 35: Perfectly Fast Colors, But Subject to Imperfections, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering with the letter B in the center against white background. 16 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 36: Pemberton Compy extra quality satteen twills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Nevins & Co. Agents. Ch. H. Crosby Lith 46 Water St. Boston. Lawrence, Mass.: Pemberton Company, ca. 1870-1872. White lettering against green background. 14 x 19 cm.
    - Item 37: Pemberton Company Lawrence, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      ____Yds. Lith. of C.H. Crosby, No. 3 Water St. Boston. Lawrence, Mass.: Pemberton Company, ca. 1857-1862. Brown lettering and design against white background. 13.5 x 18 cm. Identical to Item 38, in this folder, except for color of lettering and desig
    - Item 38: Pemberton Company Lawrence, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      ____Yds. Lith. of C.H. Crosby, No. 3 Water St. Boston. Lawrence, Mass.: Pemberton Manufacturing Company, ca. 1857-1862. Blue lettering and design against white background. Identical to Item 37, in this folder, except for color of lettering and design.
    - Item 39: Pemberton extra qual. satteen twills., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Lawrence, Mass.: Pemberton Manufacturing Company, n.d. Black lettering against gold banners set in gold, red and black border. 13.5 x 18 cm.
    - Item 40: Pemberton mills sea island., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Lawrence, Mass.: Pemberton Manufacturing Company, n.d. Probably a reference to Sea Island cotton. Gold, blue and red lettering within elaborate red and gold frame, against white background. 15.5 x 11.25 cm.
    - Item 41: Pemberton corset jeans ___________Yards., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      ____Yds. [Suncook, N.H.: Pembroke Mills, ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering against deep purple background. 14.5 x 19.5 cm.
    - Item 42: Pembroke extra heavy wigans., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Suncook, N.H.: Pembroke Mills, ca. 1860-1900. Red lettering against white background. 11 x 14.25 cm.
    - Item 43: Pembroke Mills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. Suncook, N.H.: Pembroke Mills, ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering against white background within red and gold frame. 16 x 12 cm.
    - Item 44: Pembroke superior cottons., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Suncook, N.H.: Pembroke Mills, ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering and design against white background. 23.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 45: Pembroke superior silesias, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Satin Finish. ____ Yds. [Suncook, N.H.: Pembroke Mills, ca. 1857-1870. Red lettering against white background; image of young girl in center. 8.5 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 46: Penobscot Sheeting, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against deep blue background. 20 x 15 cm.
    - Item 47: Pepperell Abbotsford percale type 180 sheets pillow cases, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Size before hemming 45 x 38 1/2. Boston: Pepperell Manufacturing Company, ca. 1940s. Images of woman and man in colonial dress on left- and right-hand sides of label. 9.5 x 7.25 cm.
    - Item 48: Pepperell Abbotsford percale type 180 sheets pillow cases size before hemming 45 x 38 1/2., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Size before hemming 45 x 38 1/2. Boston: Pepperell Manufacturing Company, ca. 1940s. Images of woman and man in colonial dress on left- and right-hand sides of label. 9.5 x 7.25 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 49: Pepperell Mang. Co. Biddeford Maine., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.d. White lettering against blue background within gold, red, and blue frame. 12.25 x 18 cm.
    - Item 50: Pepperell Mills extra heavy D warranted indigo blue, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Yds. [Biddeford, Me.: Pepperell Manufacturing Co., ca. 1800s. Black lettering against orange background. 25 x 20 cm.
    - Item 51: Perkins Mills A Drillings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Warranted Indigo Blue. Yds. Philadelphia (Manayunk), Pa.: Perkins Mills, ca. 1860-1861. Black lettering against orange background. 25.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 52: Perkins Mills extra fine shirtings., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Philadelphia (Manayunk), Pa.: Perkins MIlls, ca. 1860s. Red and gold lettering and border against white background. 19.5 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 53: Permanent Finish, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering on very thin paper. 24 x 5 cm.
    - Item 54: Persian Lawn, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. 27 1/2. 20 Yds. Name & label registered & copyright. N.p., ca. 1890. Image appears to depict three flowers, with the image of a young woman pasted into the center of the top flower, and "Persian" and "Lawn" on white banners in the center of the tw
    - Item 55: Persian Lawn, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Cette qualite est toujours la meme (This quality is always the same.) N.p., n.d. Embossed; image of young woman wearing Persian-style costume (?) in pink oval frame. 14 x 18.75 cm.
    - Item 56: Persian Twill, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering within white oval surrounded by pink and gold frame. 13 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 57: Peruvian Silk Wool, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Image of vicuna on mountainside, with other vicunas in background. 24 x 16.75 cm.
    - Item 58: Manufactured at the Philadelphia Penitentiary: warrented fast colours, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. .. Yds. ca. 1800-1820. Image depicts two-story building with cupola and weathervane; title printed on banner across top of label. The image is of the Walnut Street Jail (later the Walnut Street Prison) in Philadelphia. 9.75 x 7.75 cm.
    - Item 59: Pequea Mills. Mount Vernon Mills. Cottonades, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Philadelphia, Pa.: William Wood & Co., ca 1880. Label has been trimmed. Image of young woman at printing machine. 12.25 x 11.25 cm.
    - Item 60: Philadelphia Carpet Mills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Thos. L. Leedom & Co., 2419 Howard Street. Pattern, Color, Register, Yards. Philadelphia, Pa.: Bailey, Banks & Biddle [litho?], ca. 1880s. The letters "T L L & C" are intertwined in the center design. 9.5 x 13 cm.
    - Item 61: Philip Allen & Sons fast colors., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Yds. Providence, R. I.: Philip Allen & Sons, ca. 1860. Engraving depicts a woman on a balcony with a parrot; in b/w. Company was a manufacturer of calico prints. 11.5 14 cm.
    - Item 62: Floral Gifts, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      P.J.W. Case _________ Style No. ________ Yds. N.p., n.d. Image of rose in center against yellow background. 7.75 x 10.75 cm.
    - Item 63: Plymouth Cambrics HCF & Co., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Geo. W. Simons Lith. 12 School St. Boston. N.p., ca. 1860s. Black lettering against white background, with image of Native American in center. 10 x 13 cm.
    - Item 64: Plymouth Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      ___Yds. W.H. Forbes & Co. [lithographer]. N.p., ca. 1868-1875. White lettering on red banners; image of rooster in center in red, within gold border. 10.25 x 15 cm.
    - Item 65: Pocahontas Manufacturing Co., 1874; Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Entered according to Act of Congress in the year 1874 by Geo. C. Nightingale in the office of the Librarian of Congress at Wash. D.C. [Putnam, Conn.]: Pocahontas Manufacturing Co. Image depicts Pocahontas saving John Smith from execution at the hands of
    - Item 66: Pocketings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering and design against white background. 12 x 8 cm.
    - Item 67: Pontoosuc Woolen Mfg Co., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Case ____ No ____ Yds ____. Dennison Mfg. Co. [printer]. Pittsfield, Mass.: Pontoosuc Woolen Mfg. Co., ca. 1900-1920. Black lettering against cream background. 6.25 x 7.75 cm.
    - Item 68: Portland Cottons, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against deep purple background. 17.5 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 69: Portland Mf'g Co's Long Cloth, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Very Fine and Stout. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against deep purple background. 19.5 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 70: Post Nubila Phoebus [After clouds, the sun.], Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Crest with gold banner above, within blue and gold frame. 8.5 x 11 cm. (folded).
    - Item 71: Powhatan fine cottons, 1874; Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Entered according to Act of Congress in the year 1874 by Geo. C. Nightingale in the office of the Librarian of Congress at Washington, D.C. Putnam, Conn.: Powhattan Mills. Image of Indians with Pocahontas meeting English colonist (John Smith?). 19.75 x
    - Item 72: Premiere Qualite, 45 inches long, 144 inches wide, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., ca. 1860. Black/white/red/yellow; engraving of woman in Balmoral skirt. 9.50 x 14 cm.
    - Item 73: Premiere Qualite All Wool Flannels, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Fast Colors. Forbes. Lith. 265 Washn. St. Boston. N.p., ca. 1862- 1868. Gold and black lettering with flag motif in center within gold and gray frame against white background. 12 x 17 cm.
    - Item 74: Pretex: Indigo Blauwdruk, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Three Cats. Specially manufactured in Manchester [Eng.] for Pretoria Textile Wholesalers (PTY) Ltd. Pretoria, South Africa. ca. 1900s. Scroll shape, black and white lettering against red banner; image of three cats at each end of banner. 29 x 6 cm.
    - Item 75: Pride of the West Imperial Fine Muslin., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; iImage of blue jay in center; black lettering in white circle; red and gold border. 20 x 25 cm.
    - Item 76: Princeton Lawns, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Style No. ____ ____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against white background with gold border. 6.5 x 10 cm. (folded).
    - Item 77: Princeton Mills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Warranted Indigo Blue, And Printed On Their First Quality Standard Weight Sheetings. Yds. T. R. Marvin & Son, Prs. N.p., ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering and frame, against cream background. 13.5 x 19 cm.
    - Item 78: 3/4 Printed Lawn Warranted Fast Colors, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering, border and putti in center against light green background. 9.25 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 79: Progress Sleeve Lining, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against white background, within gold frame. 7.75 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 80: Providence Dying, Bleaching & Calendaring Company, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Providence, R.I. Engraving? Providence, R.I.: Providence Dyeing, Bleaching and Calendering Co., ca. 1840-1860. Image of mill building on left with horse and wagon, two men in street and sailboat in harbor in distance. 12 x 10.75 cm.
    - Item 81: Providence Dying, Bleaching & Calendaring Company, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Prov. Dying, Bleaching & Cal. Co. Wm. C. Snow's Residence. Engraving? Providence, R.I.: Providence Dyeing, Bleaching & Calendaring Co., ca. 1835. Image of houses along road. 12 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 82: Superior cambric, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Providence, R.I.: Providence Dyeing, Bleaching & Calendaring Co., n.d. Gold crest with the word Hope on top and an anchor in the middle; white background. 8 x 9.25 cm.
    - Item 83: The Puritan, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Engraved and copyrighted by John A. Lowell & Co., Boston, No. 4; artist initials FDM in right-hand corner. N.p., ca. 1875-1900. Image of woman peeling apples while rocking cradle. 18.25 x 23.5 cm.
    - Item 84: Puritan Denims, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Image of Puritan woman in center, wearing cape and cap; gold and black lettering against light tan background; gold and red border. 22.5 x 18.5 cm.
    - Item 85: Puritan Ticking, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Image of Puritan woman wearing cap and cape in center, light tan background with gold lettering; gold and red border. 23 x 18.25 cm.
  - Q, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Quaker Indigo Blue Drilling, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Yards. N.p., n.d. Red lettering against cream background. 25.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 2: Quality Always the Best. Our Motto., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Trade Mark. All stylish colors in their season. N.p., n.d. Label contains several images: in the center is a horseshoe with "Quality Always the Best Our Motto" inscribed on it. Within the horseshoe is the image of a woman on the left with a long-hair
    - Item 3: Quidnick, R.I. Providence, R.I., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Engraving. N.p., ca. 1850-1860. Image of mill complex with railroad; horse and buggy with two men and woman in front. 11.25 x 9 cm.
    - Item 4: Quinnebeaug Extra Weight Flannels, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Yds. Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works. Danielson, Conn.? Quinebaug Co.?, n.d. Red lettering against yellow background. 25.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 5: Quinnebaug Steam Mills Extra Fine Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 4)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. [Danielson, Conn.? Quinebaug Company? ca. 1800s. Black lettering; image of female warrior in center surmounted by eagle, with banner underneath reading Sic Semper Tyrannis (Thus Always to Tyrants). 12.5 x 15.5 cm.
  - R, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: R M, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering within red and green circle, surrounded by octagonal frame. 6.5 x 6.5 cm.
    - Item 2: Radha Krishna Khattry, Calcutta, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Malcolm Ross & Sons. Registered Trade Mark No. 36021. Calcutta. Manchester, Eng., n.d. Blue, gold and white crest on white background; red and blue border; black lettering. Used by company for customer in Calcutta; Ross was a manufacturer and exporte
    - Item 3: Radha Krishna Khattry, Calcutta, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Item 4: Rainbow Fine Cottons, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Forbes Co. [lithographer]. N.p., ca. 1880s. Image of woman and man under umbrella on edge of lake; woman is pointing out rainbow to the left. 23 x 18.25 cm.
    - Item 5: Randolph Manufacturing Company, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Forbes Co. Boston [Lithographer]. Franklinville, N.C.: Randolph Mfg. Co., ca. 1800s. White lettering against black background; with red and green border. 19.5 x 25.25 cm.
    - Item 6: Randolph Mills Bridal Quilt, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
      No. Qrs. N.p., n.d. Image of young woman in bed covered by what is called a quilt, but looks woven. 10 x 13 cm.
    - Item 7: Raw Silk, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Victor Chop. Inspected by Nippon Ki-ito, Kaisha, Ltd. Made in Japan. Japan, ca. 1900s. Image of samurai warrior with bow and arrows against light green background. 12 x 15 cm.
    - Item 8: Reading Steam Mills Neversink Sea-Island Cotton, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
      J.W. Orr, N.Y. [engraver]. Reading, Pa.? ca. 1850-1887. Tan lettering and image of mill building against white background. 16.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 9: Red Cross Cambric, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)
      _____Yds. N.p., n.d. Red lettering and red cross (similar to but not idential to Red Cross) against white background. 13 x 15.5 cm.
    - Item 10: Red Cross Cambric, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 5)